Guide to the John Watts Papers, 1945-1982 MSS.093
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series IX: Audio Recordings
  - Subseries A: Watts - Works on Tape
    - AUDIO RECORDINGS - WORKS ON TAPE Continued, undated (Box 54, Folder data_value_missing_cffa395cab21734397c330aa0ad3ae79)
    - Signals Note: Composers Fest. Orch (Demo) Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 54, Folder data_value_missing_10a9b387a6d10f59b78fe7070dddb2d2)
    - Signals Note: Random sounds from Signals Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 54, Folder data_value_missing_286ca9973c2bbfdbc470b1e5740d030e)
    - Signals Note: (Electronic) Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 54, Folder data_value_missing_82eafd17122861bba6d5d9b738a1f512)
    - Signals Note: Rehearsal Tape, Composers Fest Orch, mono Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 54, Folder data_value_missing_d6a914320556e050c4cee6d8078debe3)
    - Signals Note: Orch. Dub from test pressing Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 54, Folder data_value_missing_b68540802abe261928b93b93aafdf3d1)
    - Signals Note: Orch version from test pressing Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 54, Folder data_value_missing_a18029f9aff08432f8cae1c848ba489d)
    - Signals Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 54, Folder data_value_missing_9918b26349210bc11ce13fa3214e5ef1)
    - Signals Note: Warning, Random, 4 bells Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 54, Folder data_value_missing_d2b2a87a1f524ade42777a8d14f39464)
    - Sonata for Piano Note: Dean Sanders, 7.5ips, half-tk stereo Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 54, Folder data_value_missing_fc0f2ce5fcac28a910a8ecef424a1d66)
    - Sonata for Piano; Introix for ARP 1971; Introix for Tape construction for modern dance 1970 Note: David Del Tredici, piano, 7.5 ips Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm. (Box 54, Folder data_value_missing_3540e043406daed95a47a05c077d5ae2)
    - Sonata for Piano Note: David Del Tredici, piano, 7.5 ips Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 54, Folder data_value_missing_ab0d22ffd42a4ddb933c4b53c020d671)
    - Sonata for Piano Note: David Del Tredici, piano [Acetate disk masters inside tape box] Format: Acetate disks, undated (Box 54, Folder data_value_missing_d473d9747226493b952a60b9d63024e6)
    - Sonata for Piano Note: David Del Tredici Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 54, Folder data_value_missing_cb851d545a64576bece3656990e12400)
    - Sonata for Piano Note: David Del Tredici; Concert 1966 Carnegie Recital Hall, also piece by Robt. Longworthy Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm. (Box 54, Folder data_value_missing_ff20c92e7346e20de555b752ae6160ad)
    - Sonata for Piano Note: Peltzer, Serenus Recording Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 54, Folder data_value_missing_f83958e650f99dd2069d189f35f47ef2)
    - Sonata for Piano Note: Carnegie concert 1966, with David Del T. including pieces by Longworthy, Korte Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" (Box 54, Folder data_value_missing_b1091857a0d86bfb218b866ebd69094c)
    - Sonata for Piano Note: Dean Sanders, 7.5ips, 2-track stereo; also included Burrill Phillips' First Piano Sonata Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4", undated (Box 54, Folder data_value_missing_ad1d65e949ed4fe6c2c9ef4652d5fe99)
    - Stein piece Note: Work tape Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 55, Folder data_value_missing_6590c025fe838c13bd8bcf4a4e8bb174)
    - Stein, Gertrude Note: Stein reads from her works, Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 55, Folder data_value_missing_c6890122975dd6e6387474ac1377be16)
    - Foreman Dance, undated (Box 55, Folder data_value_missing_e27b575a69dcce52d8e638631e0c37d9)
    - Still Life Note: Hubie and Laura dialogue, 11/14/1972 Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm. (Box 55, Folder data_value_missing_9e175ce0f81798869642d1ab7593cb8c)
    - Still Life Note: Mina talking and whistling Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 55, Folder data_value_missing_2abd4e99b0c31df5e6c1d949870bd230)
    - Still Life Note: Mina squawks Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 55, Folder data_value_missing_467d20c77c55dc1e14222089338cef4e)
    - Still Life Note: Songanddance (Performance Version) ATL 3/73; Lecture demo Song and Dance, Master Performance Tape Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 55, Folder data_value_missing_1a2fb2d84500dcd1dd4740ba2befc673)
    - Still Life Note: Master 7.5 ips, stereo Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4"sm., undated (Box 55, Folder data_value_missing_ae0359ec5a9b717cc692bb6bbbb60e23)
    - Still Life; Epic-Cycles Note: Two Dance Scores with tape collage (Moog synthesizer) 1971 for Channel 13, ABC Rochester (7.5 ips). Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm. (Box 55, Folder data_value_missing_83b65fde154d4690d03fa1b15d4f6c1c)
    - Still Life Note: Leftover dialogue Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 55, Folder data_value_missing_1ad43d8dbccc6ec860e1e2f8b23e53bf)
    - Still Life Note: Lecture tape Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 55, Folder data_value_missing_cfee18f6ee1daa274a5677d6091e9b7a)
    - Still Life Note: Lecture demo, Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 55, Folder data_value_missing_23fa6d117a7960409fb68d76656339a8)
    - Song & Dance, Locrian, undated (Box 55, Folder data_value_missing_5bff63d802aab665651db5f48ab40720)
    - St. Peters Note: Shawn/Grieve/Margot Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 55, Folder data_value_missing_06d52edc8cb9af10f80066a5b78cf3f4)
    - St. Peters Note: Voices Hank, Amy, Etc. Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 55, Folder data_value_missing_161ac8b4f5c62848bd66915667d01713)
    - St. Peters Note: Voices, 1/2 track mono Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 55, Folder data_value_missing_a64034a96b4188f163c9937696c83f40)
    - Stretched #2 Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4", undated (Box 55, Folder data_value_missing_c325cc11ec6d592577cb6f7af70e44b7)
    - Stretched #3 Note: Phillips No. 2; also on the tape Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4", undated (Box 55, Folder data_value_missing_f1b538cfc76fe2a1ca19d6852a034d14)
    - Stretched #5 Note: Phillips Sonata 1 and 2 Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4", undated (Box 55, Folder data_value_missing_ce7c7a4af768d461198fc7bd5fcbe953)
    - Stretched #6 Note: Phillips Sonata 1 Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4", undated (Box 55, Folder data_value_missing_45b78c264bd0cdbb13046a5ac1385d44)
    - Suite for Solo Violin; Fantasy for Violin and Piano Note: 2 copies: Jesse Ceci, violin; DDT piano, Tison Street, violin 7.5ips, half-track stereo [demo]. Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 55, Folder data_value_missing_a0888293ef5416ae6604cb498b06afab)
    - Suite for Solo Violin Note: Ceci, violin Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 55, Folder data_value_missing_7e9b89002b3156c277bd9a75eb182121)
    - Tarot Cards Note: Last Supper 15ips drowning Brand: Scotch Format: 1/2", undated (Box 55, Folder data_value_missing_60390e44a730b123db832ecbf39296d7)
    - A Time Note: new - watts-foreman Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 55, Folder data_value_missing_1bb212838ca658f46f6958a25baa39f7)
    - A Time Note: new-copy Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 55, Folder data_value_missing_ecedd6dc1932ebc612bd8282b79e741c)
    - Time Coded Woman III Note: I-Islands track; II-Repeated; III-Warning Excerpts Brand: Scotch Format: 1/2", undated (Box 56, Folder data_value_missing_7860235ae53eed935680b749abb0a74e)
    - Time Coded Woman III Note: Sound Tracks Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4", undated (Box 56, Folder data_value_missing_8df9bbe08e12c54df78af1aabaabfc91)
    - Time Coded Woman III Note: Sound Tracks Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4", undated (Box 56, Folder data_value_missing_ccf235a11051dc8b19bcb78fdaf4bbbc)
    - Time Coded Woman Note: Cooper Union, 15 ips Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4", undated (Box 56, Folder data_value_missing_0bae807cdf556fc59a3645838bf95b7e)
    - Time Coded Woman III Note: Track 1-Islands, track II-Warnings Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 56, Folder data_value_missing_88c57c77b49d9a291fdb527dde209ca7)
    - Time Coded Woman Note: BAM Performance 4/3/82; John's score Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 56, Folder data_value_missing_cbec1ec6f7f13a0c88d6e5c6b3deb3d9)
    - Time Coded Woman Note: Cooper Union Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 56, Folder data_value_missing_b2883a8b32a8fa82241dc14c5138f72a)
    - Tinawn Note: 15ips Brand: Scotch Format: 1/2", undated (Box 56, Folder data_value_missing_14b469bde3924f30916efe9c62bf68f5)
    - Trumpets Note: Mixes Brand: Scotch Format: 1/2", undated (Box 56, Folder data_value_missing_62bc1a5b6598adce3f580b1d3a3271dc)
    - Trumpets Note: Ch. 1 only, Mixes Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 56, Folder data_value_missing_0f29fdad66b0dee7fdf46345e681a344)
    - AUDIO RECORDINGS - WORKS ON TAPE Continued, undated (Box 56, Folder data_value_missing_063080ebe8317eb8ae803e99da32cc0a)
    - UPS Note: Rough, 15ips Format: 1/2", undated (Box 56, Folder data_value_missing_305e3f5fb0e4b5344c43bd71ed14387a)
    - UPS Note: 7.5 ips Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 56, Folder data_value_missing_3574e8369245680aa9f24417af0db769)
    - UPS Note: Rough version Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 56, Folder data_value_missing_c0e05e1efbdb45aae633b59575f08807)
    - UPS, MAS Note: Re-do Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 56, Folder data_value_missing_b1b5152cbe6f72b287da5225c2e10ff4)
    - UPS Note: 1977 7.5ips, half-tk stereo [demo] Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm. (Box 56, Folder data_value_missing_926e673c188689bb10005f5016d67757)
    - UPS, ELEGY Note: 7.5 ips, half-tk [demo] Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 56, Folder data_value_missing_72ca81bca7fe78b1bc5b6fe787bccfe5)
    - Ur-Master Note: Roughs Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4", undated (Box 57, Folder data_value_missing_00a13dd11bbc0e5f6df8f3acedb131ee)
    - Ur-Master Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4", undated (Box 57, Folder data_value_missing_6e745ce6711ab1cff45e3534261b25e0)
    - Ur-Master Note: Stereo, Mother Nature Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 57, Folder data_value_missing_b8a3c109ea9ed054053d27baf46794fd)
    - Video Piece Note: Quad tape, Screen III, surf, wind Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 57, Folder data_value_missing_c44d193ba324892693d42f0ecf1e9d68)
    - Video Piece Note: Quad tape A, Screen II, 17.5 ips, bubbly water Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 57, Folder data_value_missing_964cb5dbb7f7d8568099b05e92713aa3)
    - Video Piece Note: Quad tape B, Screen I, 7.5 ips, rain, gurgles Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 57, Folder data_value_missing_729c88d45795e05416d7d2c457bdd0d4)
    - WARP Note: 4-channel 15ips Brand: Scotch Format: 1/2", undated (Box 57, Folder data_value_missing_2206876d554a99427cab7e3c17cbfebf)
    - WARP Note: 4-channel 15ips; ARP synthesizer part Format: 1/2", undated (Box 57, Folder data_value_missing_dc93603efc1d026d73786dd433c68b84)
    - WARP Note: Tape 1, Ch. 1 & 2, 7.5 ips Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 57, Folder data_value_missing_e1f459fea224c0eb1fab96d69b7e1464)
    - WARP Note: Stereo Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 57, Folder data_value_missing_d214c1fcb0bfbf33b8ae88c0d8070237)
    - WARP Note: Performance by Iowa Brass Quintet, and John Watts, ARP;7.5 ips, half-tk stereo Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 57, Folder data_value_missing_74c3e732d446e623c07f804b70e076b3)
    - WARP Note: Tape 2, Ch. 3 & 4, 7.5 ips" Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 57, Folder data_value_missing_b5fe280b126c5e4a915f154bf76ffe18)
    - Wicked John and the Devil Note: for narrator, ballad singer, and chamber ensemble, 7.5 ips, mono Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 57, Folder data_value_missing_d0c7640d2caec6e98483fe62f7470335)
    - Wicked John and the Devil Note: "Q. Doolittle, Violin, University Chamber Players, Quenten D. director" Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 57, Folder data_value_missing_ca228ccf976d13e5533f6502f9c0dd5f)
    - Wicked John Rehearsal Note: 1966 Quenten Doolittle Brand: Ampex Format: 1/4" sm. (Box 57, Folder data_value_missing_c18624a4a036220a8289e344da8db954)
    - Wicked John Rehearsal Note: Edited tape w/ harmonica Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 57, Folder data_value_missing_bf2158b66f9926663e3a0f3f54ce092e)
    - Wicked John Rehearsal for Dance Note: 1970 Tape construction Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm. (Box 57, Folder data_value_missing_c7fbb3d670903b8c0808d30f52cb19a4)
    - Wicked John Rehearsal Note: St. Peter's tape, 1970 Master Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm. (Box 57, Folder data_value_missing_404c2e01d31bdc3e589c031108f2a8ef)
    - Watts II Note: "mono, quad, faders.. ." Brand: Scotch Format: 1/2", undated (Box 57, Folder data_value_missing_767489c9304924ab4332287372e1b7e5)
    - UPS/MAS Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 57, Folder data_value_missing_535bfc4de2c3f51a3d5965de705373de)
    - WARP, Introix Note: stereo Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 57, Folder data_value_missing_1755e7769f963080c1246351c94479e7)
    - Hank's tape Note: New-Odd bits Brand: Sony Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 57, Folder data_value_missing_22bc712eeb13dcab99b52fc608e73101)
  - Subseries B: Watts - Demo tapes
    Complilations and Samplers
    - Schatz, Warren Note: Outtakes from Warren's Gospel disco album Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4", undated (Box 58, Folder data_value_missing_3eee21fbf7401772e663b6bfc9312fd4)
    - Schatz, Warren Note: Outtakes from Warren's Gospel disco album Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4", undated (Box 58, Folder data_value_missing_6436aed1f27982bef5656694c5759cc0)
    - Schatz, Warren Note: Two of Warren's Tunes with ARP additions Brand: Agfa Format: 1/2", undated (Box 58, Folder data_value_missing_16c09f0ea12c18b95fbc91da93a8d6cf)
    - Watts Demo Note: Excerpts from Donnez Pas; complete Elegy and Laugharne; 7.5 ips half-tk stereo Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 58, Folder data_value_missing_43f20360acb87219c9ed41a7142c6b35)
    - Watts Demo Note: Scotch Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4", undated (Box 58, Folder data_value_missing_bb9621a7cee5d41fc82e4f0462fd7f71)
    - Watts Demo Note: Excerpts from Signals, Sonata, Epic Cycles, Fable Fair, Introix, 7.5ips, half-tk stereo Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4", undated (Box 58, Folder data_value_missing_5a481248762b3e98d137aa7b74fc11f3)
    - Watts Works Note: MAS, Laugharne, Mother Goose(Donnez Pas),Elegy Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 58, Folder data_value_missing_22bf3221c387362737dd028c27884d3a)
    - Watts Works Note: Composers Theater at New School 1977, Composers Fest. Orch. MAS, Gallery Piece, and Elegy - 15ips, two-tk stereo Brand: Basf Format: 1/4" (Box 58, Folder data_value_missing_3e8607c3dbef5708cc01dd9f2659f039)
    - Watts Demo Note: Elegy, WARP, Laugharne Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 58, Folder data_value_missing_8fc4ff38db01a06c0e1386878ebd7c35)
    - Watts Demo Note: Excerpts from film "Daisies": Islands, Finale and Gallery Piece with Robt. Levy Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 58, Folder data_value_missing_2d26f779064b528f835a13ce94db73df)
    - Watts Demo Note: Keepsakes, MAS Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 58, Folder data_value_missing_4b1e6f93528b417d3dcf8b81ae7efdc6)
    - Watts Demo Note: WARP, Memorials Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 58, Folder data_value_missing_c1a932f91da1b84f3bb1342e12d3bb76)
    - Watts Demo Note: Watts and Schatz: I've Been Wonderin' and Don't You Go Away Again, and Elegy Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 58, Folder data_value_missing_1191e3f75e30ca554668541768cab39a)
    - Watts Demo Note: "6 copies of: 1976 various pieces incl. Wrong-Headed Blues, Elegy, Theatrical (Box 58, Folder data_value_missing_69a3b88789c2986cf96779c4abc2d924)
    - preview for NY Erotic Film Fest '72, I've been wonderin, Laugharne, Signals, TV ads, The Louise Show"" for TV, other ads""" Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 58, Folder data_value_missing_5e489168a03e121f1a8b8f6ea6f28bac)
    - Watts Demo Note: 2-channel mono: NY Erotic film fest music; TV public service ads, Preacherman", Elegy" Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 58, Folder data_value_missing_5146f44e6f672639f2ab62cbd7871b28)
    - Watts Demo Note: Overture from Fable Fair, Fantasy for Violin and Piano (DDT and Tison Street), Chamber Laughs when I sit down at the piano, and Sonata for Piano (DDT) Brand: Coach Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 58, Folder data_value_missing_2fb06da3c4ca998c8aaea3f00f85be59)
    - New School Note: NS Performing Workshop Tape Fall 1975 Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" (Box 58, Folder data_value_missing_c8efedd691a50b072d0a169b38c79150)
    - Watts Electric Company Note: 12-12-80, dubbed 3-19-81" Brand: TDK Format: 1/4" sm., 19-1981" (Box 58, Folder data_value_missing_0a58613a73c880d5a8357c15d164effe)
  - Subseries C: Concerts - Live Recordings
    - May Festival 1974 Note: Yvar Mikhashoff Recital Brand: Basf Format: 1/4" (Box 59, Folder data_value_missing_4943e7cfe6455907502aefefa7571b75)
    - May Festival 1974 Note: Dwight Peltzer Recital, Whole program Brand: Basf Format: 1/4" (Box 59, Folder data_value_missing_7f551cb8af52318ee408dc9ad66818f6)
    - Effinger "Casals Trio" Note: Unedited Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 59, Folder data_value_missing_5157845700e1e569b64955d75e14c218)
    - Lloyd, Charles Note: Homage to the Universe, Big Sur Tapestry Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 59, Folder data_value_missing_d4bac079ef2583a61414876bd89bb75b)
    - Piano for Te, Maxiconcerto Note: Composers Festival Orch: 14 Jan. 1977 Brand: Basf Format: 1/4" (Box 59, Folder data_value_missing_aebfe5a9d2c2b6fb5845768810baf64f)
    - Levy, Robert Note: New Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4", undated (Box 59, Folder data_value_missing_26c1a1f743f657386ddb4a3edb5876a2)
    - Denerstein, Dan Note: 3-channel Brand: Scotch Format: 1/2", undated (Box 59, Folder data_value_missing_413d38dbdb2ec65238a1e08595b5b0f2)
    - Iowa Brass Quintet Note: Allan Blank, Paul Turok, WARP, Andrix, Husa Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4", undated (Box 59, Folder data_value_missing_1a54ed1db2eb66f0dbeaa5115ea49a32)
    - Iowa Brass Quintet Note: Andrix, Husa Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4", undated (Box 59, Folder data_value_missing_d3069b82f6a0a4051b7d8ff248f0b93f)
    - Iowa Brass Quintet Note: Watts-WARP, Turok, Concord (Brown, Crumb) May, 1971 Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" (Box 59, Folder data_value_missing_00e33782ccc24ae8f07232343ac9315b)
    - Iowa Brass Quintet Note: Blank, Turok, Watts Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4", undated (Box 59, Folder data_value_missing_ae3d9a6c92f5344708b7285a8b02ee39)
    - Turok, Paul, Sampler Note: 7.5 ips Chartres West, Finale from Brass Quintet, The Bells of Arcos Op. 30, #2, Partita for Solo Oboe, op. 15 Brand: Universal Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 59, Folder data_value_missing_97641d02ea21752b65cc0dc105eb453a)
    - Tollefson, A. piano Note: Cisterns II by Felix Powell, Piano Quartet of R. Schumann - St. Mary's College Summer Music Camp, Md. Brand: Stereo Sound Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 59, Folder data_value_missing_848eb461814ff619ed28c49612546b35)
    - Phillips-Hatcher Duo Note: demo tape - guitar and flute Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 59, Folder data_value_missing_4ca0bbcb6813a51a50275dad345fc1dc)
    - Foreman, Laura Note: Songs - music & lyrics by Laura, 1968 Brand: Sam Goody Format: 1/4" sm. (Box 59, Folder data_value_missing_154a904a02777afd459951e28e8eabc7)
    - Foreman, Laura Note: 2 tapes of: More'n a year by Laura, Sung by Charlie Brown, 1966 Brand: Audiotape Format: 1/4" sm. (Box 59, Folder data_value_missing_248f5121f253c4bdae1206b54c0627ba)
    - Foreman, Laura Note: Laura's songs - sample sections, duet Brand: Audiotape Format: 1/4" sm., undated (Box 59, Folder data_value_missing_4aa850ee40c646afa1c981833f1a3138)
    - Foreman, Laura Note: LF Audition tape 11/7/72 Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" sm., 1972 (Box 59, Folder data_value_missing_85b5ddd8a2633c6c4c930a29ac69365e)
    - May Festival 1972, CCT Concert Note: 1972 Master Dub, Composers Festival; Orch. Effinger, Tropi, Clark, Duckworth, Foley, Watts Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" (Box 60, Folder data_value_missing_5fd0712995d37d2d37306cd5395eea45)
    - May Fest 1973 Note: Brass Concert Brand: Basf Format: 1/4" (Box 60, Folder data_value_missing_b740d14b0ebe083618897d6c5c5c4a84)
    - CCT Concert Note: Gallery, Eutectics, Elegy (1st half of program) Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 60, Folder data_value_missing_1684e890d03b1fcc3c299573749917e3)
    - Watts Concert July 1974 Note: St. Mary's College: "Sonata w/ Tollefson, Elegy, Piano for Te, Gallery Piece, Signals" Brand: Basf Format: 1/4" (Box 60, Folder data_value_missing_01146d0fe6ffc470c85519bcadee0455)
    - Watts Concert April '74 Note: Buffalo May Festival Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 60, Folder data_value_missing_99fb0f324ae049becc36910c09f36892)
    - Watts Concert March '74 Note: Notes from Underground May Festival Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 60, Folder data_value_missing_589cd42916dc775dda94f85b6de326f9)
    - World Music Ensemble Note: Music of Myers, Smith, Duckworth, Wolff, Diemente, Macbride, Rec. by Fred Miller, WARP Studios Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 60, Folder data_value_missing_aaf3b9f7e1ae691fd09cb5eaa1f6ea16)
    - May Fest 1974 Note: Concord String Quartet, Whole Program Brand: Basf Format: 1/4" (Box 60, Folder data_value_missing_3664e14cca6744074703f5b5b7ea4ccd)
    - CCT Concert Note: at Greenwich Mews, October 1972 music of Moore, Rovics, Spiegelman, Pleskow, Wolpe, Brings, and Kraft Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" (Box 60, Folder data_value_missing_e84be8a7c20abc149fba130a4c3db04e)
    - CCT Concert Note: Greenwich Mews - Feb. 1973, music of Epstein, Luening, Stravinsky, Kupferman Brand: Basf Format: 1/4" (Box 60, Folder data_value_missing_114abf9761e196bd75d7f87e6a2ae55b)
    - CCT Concert Note: New Music for Trumpet with Robert Levy, Watts on ARP. Music of Andrix, Blank, Cope, Erb, Powell, and Watts. January 1973 Brand: Basf Format: 1/4" (Box 60, Folder data_value_missing_e0932466bf5a720f24e7c105b8ca2b0d)
    - CCT Concert Note: Greenwich Mews, Music of Doolittle, Wyman, Gottlieb, Schwartz; Feb.'73 Brand: Basf Format: 1/4", undated (Box 60, Folder data_value_missing_15ac11ff0bba37e65688a817b8659ffa)
    - May Festival Note: Performance group 1973 Brand: Basf Format: 1/4" (Box 60, Folder data_value_missing_96f01aac0c7ab82dd43a1759970f02e1)
    - May Festival Note: Composers Fest Orch. May 1974 Brand: Basf Format: 1/4" (Box 60, Folder data_value_missing_9d504b333066433fa3e6f2389267bcb6)
    - May Festival Note: Electronic Gala, May 1972 Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" (Box 60, Folder data_value_missing_904bf44978722da46b243106fef24146)
    - May Festival Dubs Note: Fennelly, Zupko, Watts Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4", undated (Box 60, Folder data_value_missing_94eacd5ef984a814f04b15b8202e94bd)
    - CCT Series: Trilogy Records Note: "Quad L.P. 7.5ips; Music of Ghent, Watts, Fennelly, not the master tape" Brand: Agfa Format: 1/2", undated (Box 61, Folder data_value_missing_9f4bf9300026fe42cd4f5e8c6fbc709d)
    - May Festival Note: Performance group 1973 Brand: Basf Format: 1/4" (Box 61, Folder data_value_missing_58d7ae53d1d1c02ce1d540390c6ed041)
    - May Festival Note: Composers Fest Orch. May 1974 Brand: Basf Format: 1/4" (Box 61, Folder data_value_missing_6343c225ba53747cf39d2c8eb4434bc4)
    - May Festival Note: Electronic Gala, May 1972 Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4" (Box 61, Folder data_value_missing_b656fbc535cf61a34050230470c39a9a)
    - May Festival Dubs Note: Fennelly, Zupko, Watts Brand: Scotch Format: 1/4", undated (Box 61, Folder data_value_missing_4995b30f0acee4743b8c9a1e527ec100)
    - May Festival Note: Notes from Underground, Queens Student-Faculty Ensemble 1973 Brand: Basf Format: 1/4" (Box 61, Folder data_value_missing_20b7fa79c01506bb8bbec95addc02d0a)